Hollywood's all-American boy had a secret.
Tab Hunter Confidential is a documentary film directed by Jeffrey Schwarz.
Throughout the 1950s, Tab Hunter reigned as
Hollywood’s ultimate male heartthrob.
But throughout his years of stardom, Tab had a secret.
Tab Hunter was gay, and spent his Hollywood years in a precarious closet
that repeatedly threatened to implode and destroy him.
Tab Hunter himself shares first hand, for the first time, what it was like to be a studio manufactured movie star during the
Golden Age of Hollywood and the consequences of being someone totally different from his studio manufactured image.
Self, played by Tab Hunter.
Self, played by Debbie Reynolds.
Self, played by Robert Wagner.
Self, played by John Waters.
Self, played by George Takei.
Self, played by Clint Eastwood.
Tab Hunter Confidential is a 2015 American documentary film focusing
on the American actor, singer, and author Tab Hunter.
It is inspired by his autobiography of the same name.
The film was produced by Allan Glaser and directed by Jeffrey Schwarz.
The film features extensive interviews with Hunter, as well as contemporaries and
associates, including John Waters, Clint Eastwood, Debbie Reynolds, and more.
The film explores themes of sexuality, biography, in the
closet, hollywood, based on memoir or autobiography.